{
    "id": "d1498b363354479aa5aff9cb4e5439a3",
    "title": "Too, So, And Enough",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There was ........................ much work to do.",
            "description": "Note the pattern too...to.",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "enough"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7fc85e57dd33409d9d9e207a27a743e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was ....................... much work that I got hardly any rest.",
            "description": "Note the pattern so...that.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "enough",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ca24eccfa82949ec9ae862c39dafd498"
        },
        {
            "question": "If the water is warm ........................, we may go for a swim.",
            "description": "When enough is used as an adverb, it goes after the adjective or adverb modified by it. ",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "enough",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "37fd2a8340614057bff4becb63e44b58"
        },
        {
            "question": "The room is ........................ cold. Should I put the heating on?",
            "description": "Too and so are possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "enough"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6a8e2eb8440548608a83ad72b3b2eb30"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn't buy the coat because it was .........................",
            "description": "Too shows undesirable extremes. Enough indicates sufficiency. ",
            "answers": [
                "too expensive",
                "expensive enough",
                "enough expensive"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "56ed208b8db14e1fa37e2f65bc2e90e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "We haven't got ........................ chairs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too big",
                "big enough",
                "so big"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a9f00ce6a6bd412a987afefc8f7ff3ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "The bag was ........................ heavy that I couldn't lift it.",
            "description": "Note the pattern so...that.",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "enough",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "86e1d8bd359e472e9693f58a2dccec9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He isn't ........................ to be a soldier.",
            "description": "When enough is used as an adverb, it goes after the adjective it modifies. ",
            "answers": [
                "enough tall",
                "tall enough",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e35c0c85ff0949c4929c2752f689ec6f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven't got ........................ to take a holiday.",
            "description": "Too shows undesirable extremes. Enough has a positive meaning. ",
            "answers": [
                "too much time",
                "enough time",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a17e4c675ecf4bcab6527991b1d61c9f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The room is ........................ to accommodate ten people.",
            "description": "Enough indicates sufficiency. Too shows undesirable extremes. ",
            "answers": [
                "enough spacious",
                "spacious enough",
                "too spacious"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "20ac58cc8d8d4ac19118e9d32ad3c02e"
        },
        {
            "question": "They are ....................... to buy a car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rich enough",
                "enough rich",
                "too rich"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a3dfad7bbf4a4ea9a8eedef3ff0e143a"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you drink .................... coffee, you won't get good sleep.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enough",
                "too",
                "too much"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "19fdb572038a4c7f9d4378d6ca22cde5"
        }
    ]
}